When working with Word documents,
there may be occasions where
you need to change a specific
word or words within a document.
If the document is only one page long,
that can be quite straightforward
and you can just go through
and replace each word manually.
However, when working with large
documents, it may be a case that this
is unrealistic and time-consuming.
Within Word, there is a feature called
find and replace, which would allow
you to search for specific words and
then replace them with another word.
In this example letter that I
have on the screen, I'm going to
find the word "information" and
replace that with the word "data".
I know there are several instances of
the word information, so to access the
find and replace tool, I simply go to
the edit menu button, scroll down to
select find and then select replace.
This brings up the find
and replace dialogue box.
So the word I'm looking
for is "information".
And it will highlight every instance
of the word information and I'm
going to change that with "data".
So once I'm happy, if I select
Replace All that will automatically
replace every instance of the word
"information" with the word "data".